不 玛格丽特 我希望你
No, Margaret, I want you to triple check
跟合规官再三确认这事
with the compliance officer about that.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我在搞个小发明
I'm working on a little something.
你知道你在做煎饼时
You know how when you're making pancakes,
-手上总是沾满了面糊吗 -不知道
- your hands are always full? - No.
这可以解决那个问题
Well, this'll solve that.
你是把烟雾报警器里的电池取下来做这个了吗
Did you take the batteries out of the smoke detector for this?
不 我还在 还在呢
No, no, still here. Still here.
不 我希望今天下午就看到投资者声明
Yeah, no, I want to read the investor statement this afternoon,
但是多姆 你得重新发一遍
but, Dom, you're gonna have to resend it.
你不小心把你写的小说的第一章发我了
You accidentally e-mailed me the first chapter of your novel,
给你点小意见
and just a tiny little note,
并非所有的胸都是丰满的
maybe not all bosoms are heaving.
谢了 各位
Thanks, guys.
周六早上也要打工作电话
Work call on a Saturday morning?
怎么回事
What's going on?
亲爱的
Honey.
你可能现在不想谈这个
You probably don't want to get into this right now,
但这到底是秃了一块还是发旋的中心
but is this a bald spot or the center of your swirl?
我的工作简直太惨了
My job has been miserable.
我总在工作 连睡觉的时间都没有
I'm always working, I never sleep,
我整天做的就是给别人擦屁股
and all I do is clean up other people's messes
因为我是所有人中唯一的成年人
because I'm the only adult in the room.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我这是又当妈了
I'm a mom again,
但我的孩子却是一帮我不爱的人
but to people I don't love.
亲爱的 听我说
Sweetheart, listen.
多年来 你一直支持着我
For years, you supported me
任我在房地产行业耍 以及玩杂耍
while I juggled realtoring and -- and juggling.
现在轮到我来支持你了
And now it's my turn to support you.
有任何困难 直接找我
Anything that's not work, I'm your guy.
天啊
Oh, God!
瞧瞧你们啊 玩得很开心嘛
Hey, look at you guys. So playful.
等我结婚了
When I get married,
我希望我和我老婆永远不要失去这种怪念头
I hope my wife and I never lose that sense of whimsy.
-谢谢你 卢克 -你有什么事
- Thank you, Luke. - What do you want?
好吧 我就老实交代吧
Okay, here's the deal.
我兄弟斯库特和我
My buddy Scooter and I
想出了一个超赞的商业点子
came up with this really cool business idea.
我们觉得一定会大获成功的
We think it's gonna be huge.
那真是太好了 小老弟
That's great, pal!
我们太为你骄傲了啊
We are so proud of you.
直接说弊端吧
Get to the bad part.
没有弊端
There is no bad part.
实际上 你们还能多赚点钱
Actually, you guys are gonna make money.
因为我打算退学创业 这样就省下学费了
Because I have to drop out of school to do it.
你绝对不能退学
You're not dropping out of school.
-亲爱的 -别
- Honey... - No.
我来处理
I -- I got this.
不过我们应该能预料到会有这么一天
But we should've seen it coming.
毕竟他老爹是"嘿 面糊"牌面糊挤压器的发明者
After all, his dad is the creator of the Hey Batter, Batter.
名字只是暂用 很可能已经被人注册了
The name's a placeholder.
但非常可能还没人用
But probably still available.
爸 我希望你知道我超爱你的面糊发射器
Dad, I want you to know I love your pancake shooter.
那你看到这个改进版的...
Have you seen the updates...to...
即冷型吸管了吗
the Insta-Cold straw?
你应该作为名人被印在邮票上
You should be on a stamp.
那东西有不电到人的时候吗
Has that ever not electrocuted someone?
有时候你必须先电击一些人
Sometimes you have to shock a few people
才能让世界有触电般的震撼
before you shock the world.
这句话该附在你的邮票上
That should go on your stamp.
够了 别再恭维你爸了
Okay, stop flattering your dad.
你绝不能退学
You're not dropping out of school.
你就快毕业了啊
You're almost done!
更重要的是
And more importantly,
我们这个家绝不允许半途而废
we don't quit things in this family.
海莉就从大学退学了
Haley quit college.
艾丽克斯中止了她在南极的工作
And Alex quit her job in Antarctica.
爸爸也从没完成过一个数独
And Dad has never finished a Sudoku.
那太难了
They are hard.
妈 这不是在瞎闹
Mom, this isn't some goof.
斯库特和我真的很看好这个点子能成功
Scooter and I really believe in this idea.
至少能让我们向你们展示下
Can we at least show you
今天下午的投资人介绍会吗
in the investor presentation this afternoon?
我们很乐意去听听 对吧
We'd love to hear it, wouldn't we?
当然了
Of course.
太好了 你们一定不会失望的
Yes! You guys aren't gonna be disappointed.
我这就去打给斯库特
I'm gonna call Scooter now.
他绝对不能退学
He's not dropping out of school.
你必须用开放的思想去听
You have got to listen with an open mind.
毕竟
After all,
如果所有父母都强迫自己的孩子待在学校
what kind of world would we live in if all parents forced their kids
不去追求梦想 那我们会生活在什么样的世界
to stay in school and not pursue their dreams?
没有史蒂夫·乔布斯 没有马克·扎克伯格
No Steve Jobs, no Mark Zuckerberg,
没有超模辛迪·克劳馥
no Cindy Crawford.
史蒂夫·乔布斯将电脑装进了大家的口袋里
Steve Jobs put a computer in everyone's pocket.
卢克差点死于在电动扶梯上脱帽衫
Luke almost died taking off a hoodie on an escalator.
我要表达的重点是 梦想是需要培育的
My point is, dreams need to be fostered.
说老实话
And if I'm being honest,
我还挺乐意担任那两个年轻人的导师的
I kind of love the idea of being a mentor to these two young minds.
木勺子
Wooden spoon!
快用木勺子隔断连接
Knock it away with a wooden spoon!
谢谢救命之恩
Thank you.
这简直太棒了
Oh, this is amazing!
天啊
Oh, my God.
大爸的走路姿势就是那样的
Daddy so walks like that!
你们为什么笑成这样
Why are you guys laughing?
因为 因为我们开心
We -- We were happy?
从什么时候开始的
Since when?
你们又在看那个视频吗
Were you watching that video again?
最近 高中学校的海豚吉祥物
Recently, the high school dolphin mascot
在橄榄球比赛期间 一直在模仿小卡的动作
has been, uh, mocking Cam during football games.
他简直是个... 我一般很少用这个词夸人
He's -- and I don't use this word lightly --
天才
a genius.
在比赛中用用脑子不行吗
How about we get our heads in the game?!
瑞克 你要从中间飞奔过去
Rick, you're gonna be streaking through.
所以要撞开别人飞快地穿过去 明白吗
So it's gonna be boom, boom. You got it?
我很惊讶你竟然无法
I'm surprised you can't see the humor
从那个吉祥物的行为中感受到幽默
in what the mascot is doing.
这跟扮小丑很像不是吗
Isn't it a lot like clowning?
-你刚说什么 -你是疯了吗
- What did you just say? - Are you insane?
扮吉祥物跟小丑表演完全不一样
Mascot-ing is nothing like clowning!
小丑是宫廷小丑的后代
Clowns are descendants of the court jester,
是国王的忠实谏臣
truth-teller to the king.
吉祥物根本不懂什么真善美
Mascots know nothing of veritas and beauty.
你们不就是折气球做小狗吗
Don't you just make wiener dogs out of balloons?
你这是嫉妒 因为没有小孩子会说
You are just jealous because no kid ever said,
"妈妈 今年我的生日能请一位
"Hey, Mom, this year for my birthday,
缉毒警察来吗"
can we get a narc?"
好吧 我很抱歉
Okay, look, I'm -- I'm sorry.
我压力山大 这个吉祥物让我很不爽
I'm just stressed out. This mascot is under my skin!
今天我不能让他害我出丑
I can't have him making me look like a fool today.
我刚得知一位
I just found out a recruiter
北中央密苏里大学的猎头
from the University of North Central Missouri
要来看我执教
is coming to watch me coach.
猎头
A recruiter?
你申请了密苏里州的工作吗
Did you apply for a job in Missouri?
我只说了我有空
I just said I was available.
都没跟我商量商量
W-Without consulting me?
你不是一直说可以接受
Well, you always said you were okay
全家搬回密苏里吗
with moving back to Missouri at some point,
把我们的小家乐变成农家乐
turning our little family into a "farmily."
你知道我很讨厌那个词
You know I hate that word.
为什么 意思清楚还很有趣啊
Why? It's descriptive and fun.
而且你知道吗 如果我得到这份工作
And you know what? Look, if I got this job,
我就会是历史上第一个公开出柜的
I would be the first openly gay college football coach
大学橄榄球教练
in history,
我以为你会支持的
and I would think you'd support that.
我也以为你会先问过我之后
And I would think that you would ask me
才举家搬迁搞农家乐
before uprooting our whole farmily --
该死 我被洗脑了
Damn it, it's in there now!
你们好呀 小可爱们
Hello, mis ninos.
谢谢你帮我们照看几小时宝宝
Thank you so much for watching the babies for a few hours.
如果你分不清谁是谁
If you have trouble telling them apart,
就脱掉他们的纸尿裤
just take off their diapers.
我在乔治的纸尿裤里面写了他的名字
I wrote George's name inside his.
我的曾孙们来了
There's my great-grandchildren.
他们能认人了吗
Do they recognize faces?
我需要给他们塞点钱
Do I need to start slipping them cash
好让他们知道谁才是老大吗
to let them know who's in charge?
外公 你不用花钱贿赂他们
Grandpa, you don't need to buy their love.
给我吧 我会把你夸上天
Buy mine, and I'll talk you up.
我们要照顾宝宝吗 我要不要取消高尔夫球
Are we babysitting? Should I cancel golf?
不不不 我知道让你跟你的朋友
No, no, no, no, I know how important it is
一起抱怨现在的年轻人
for you and your friends to complain about
跟你们那一代人
how young people today
不太一样是多么重要
are slightly different than your generation.
范·迪塞尔就是嘴里不含棒棒糖
Vin Diesel is just Telly Savalas
没什么名言的泰利·萨拉瓦斯而已
without the lollipop and a great catchphrase.
好了 你俩 我知道新手爸妈的二人时光
Okay, and you two, I know how precious alone time is
有多宝贵
for new parents,
-所以你们都走吧 -拜拜
- so everybody go. - Bye-bye!
下午玩得开心哦
Have a great afternoon!
好了 小可爱们 歌洛莉亚为你们
Okay, mis niños, Gloria has planned
安排好了一个刺激的下午
a very exciting afternoon for you.
你们看
Let's see.
准备好拒绝撒旦
Who is ready to reject Satan
和他的空头支票了吗
and all his empty promises?
今天 我要偷偷地给宝宝们施洗礼
Today, I'm having the babies secretly baptized,
让他们成为天主教徒 和加入我们这个成员间
both into Catholicism and into the crazy things
互相恶搞的疯狂家庭
we do to each other in this family.
-绝对不行 -讲点道理 扎西
- Absolutely not! - Okay, be reasonable, Tashi.
今晚对我来说是个很重要的比赛
I -- Tonight's a big game for me.
我必须表现出我的权威
I -- I need to project authority,
可你这样捣乱破坏了我的权威
and your antics undermine me.
那就做好准备吧 教练
Well, buckle up, Coach,
因为我要继续搞大事情
'cause I'm taking it up a giant notch
把今天的比赛录下来放到我的大学申请里
and taping today's game for my college apps.
你肯定能进大学的啊
Okay, you're gonna get into college.
你成绩很亮眼
You have fantastic grades.
你说得可对了呢 成绩很好的亚洲小孩
Oh, you're right -- an Asian kid with great grades.
真新鲜
That's fresh.
我必须确保能被录取
I need to guarantee a spot.
扮吉祥物就让我很有特点
Mascot-ing sets me apart.
听好了 臭小鬼
Listen, you little punk.
我可以禁你的赛
I could suspend you.
你的梦想大学看到
How would your fancy colleges
这个记录会怎么想呢
like to see that on your record, huh?
想得美
Nice try,
但是根据最高法院
but, uh, my free expression
在北达科达州诉班迪托案中的裁决
is protected by the Supreme Court ruling
我的自由表达权是受到保护的
in North Dakota vs. Bandito.
你 你这个窃取中场光芒的小偷
Oh, you -- you halftime hacks.
毫无良知 毫无荣誉
No scruples, no honor.
这又是在为小丑的事不爽吗
Is this a clown thing again?
我们小丑一根
We clowns have more humanity
精灵古怪的超大号小指头
in one of our whimsically oversized pinkies,
也比穿着臭烘烘连身公仔服的你要有人性
more than you do in your entire stinky costume.
你个油头粉面的精英主义者
You powder-faced elitists,
戴着你的红鼻子瞧不起所有人
looking down your red noses at everybody!
你清醒一点吧
Wipe the pie out of your eyes.
革命就要开始了
The revolution is coming!
-我们非得在周六做吗 -抱歉
- Do we really need to do this on a Saturday? - I'm sorry.
尼克本来应该在
Nick was supposed to sign these
他去斐济之前签好的
before he left for Fiji...
而且大家都得领工资了
...and people need to get paid.
我们可不都住这种豪宅
We don't all live in mansions.
这算什么豪宅 玛格丽特
This is hardly a mansion, Margaret.
我们为什么要给个萨满法师开这么大的支票
Whoa, why are we writing a huge check to a shaman?
尼克根据萨满预言招实习生
Oh, Nick took the interns on a vision quest.
至少女实习生是这样
Well, the female ones.
真恶心
Gross.
大家好 斯库特[滑板车]到了
Hey, guys. Scooter's here.
太好了
Great.
等不及要听听这个绝佳的点子了
Can't wait to hear this amazing idea.
等等 等等
Hang on, hang on, hang on, hang on.
还记得我们说要立场一致
Can we just remember we're on the same team
绝不能让卢克退学吗
and Luke can't drop out of school?
所以别让我当坏人啊
So please don't make me the bad guy.
亲爱的 他们都还是孩子
Honey, they're kids.
我不想打击他们的志气
I don't want to crush their spirit.
他们只是
They're just --
他们只是想寻求一点指引
They're just looking for a little guidance.
那我们就指引他们回到大学里
Oh, we're gonna guide them right back into college.
玛格丽特 稍等我几分钟
Margaret, this is gonna take a few minutes.
我们去客厅 你可以在这等会儿吗
Do you mind hanging here while we're in the living room?
我就在这间客厅等着好了
I'll just wait here in this other living room.
老天 暴殄空间啊
My God, the waste.
爸妈 这位是斯库特·李维尔
Mom, Dad, this is Scooter Rivael.
-菲尔 克莱尔 幸会 -你好
- Phil, Claire, nice to meet you. - Hi.
卢克对你们二位赞誉有加
Luke said such wonderful things.
等等 你就是斯库特吗
Wait. Um, you're -- you're Scooter?
我本以为会是更年轻一点的人
I-I was expecting someone younger,
穿滚轮鞋 背双肩书包之类的
maybe wearing Heelys and a backpack.
我真名叫斯考特
Uh, well, my real name's Scott,
不过在我和卢克相遇的俱乐部里
but Luke and I met at the club
大家都叫我斯库特
where everyone calls me Scooter.
或更难听的名字
Or worse.
我们来听听你们的发财大计吧
So, let's hear this big idea, huh?
好 像我们排练的那样说
Okay. Well, just like we rehearsed it.
你可以的 兄弟
You got this, buddy.
还记得之前我白天吃夜间服用的药
Remember when I took nighttime medicine in the daytime
结果摔下楼梯了吗
and fell down the stairs?
还用问吗
Yeah. Remember?
是我把你脱臼的十根手指一根根扳回去
I bent all your fingers back into their sockets.
之后我不得不去看了三种科目的医生
Well, I had to go to three different doctors,
每个医生都叫我填写同样的表格
and every one of them made me fill out the same forms.
隆重介绍 医疗填表器
Introducing FormFiller Med,
这是个安全加密的手机应用
a secure encrypted mobile app
只需用手机轻碰一下 你的医疗和保险信息
that transfers your medical and insurance info
就能转发到你医生的办公室
to your doctor's office with a tap of your phone.
不用再反复填写同样的无聊表格
No more filling out the same boring forms over and over again.
我给俱乐部几个老家伙说了这个点子
I ran the idea by a couple old guys at the club,
-他们都很喜欢 -对 而且我们当时还没醉
- and they loved it. - Yeah, and we weren't even drunk yet.
酗酒每天导致数百万人丧命 并不好笑
Alcoholism kills millions of people a day.
我知道你们在想什么
I know what you're thinking --
医生会支持吗
Will doctors go for this?
我们调查了两百多位医生和医务人员
We polled over 200 doctors and medical personnel,
93%的人说很乐意付我们月费
and 93% said that they would happily pay our monthly fee
来减轻他们的管理负担
to reduce their administrative load.
但医生办公室
But don't, uh, doctor's offices
不都用各自的系统吗
all use, like, different systems?
问得好 克莱尔
Great question, Claire.
最大的两个医疗软件系统
The top two medical software systems
市场占有率为90%
have 90% market share,
我们与这两个都兼容
and we're compatible with both.
厉害 那你负责做什么 斯库特
Wow. And, uh, what do you do, Scooter?
我指除了跟小孩交朋友之外
Other than befriend children, I mean.
我是风险投资人
I'm a venture capitalist.
我在过去30几年里 投资了22家公司
I've invested in 22 companies over the last 30 years
并亲自带领其中三家
and personally led three of them
从初始概念发展到首次公开募股
from initial concept through IPO.
了不起
Fascinating.
你有没有考虑过跟你自己儿子
You ever thought about starting a business
一起创业呢
with, um, I don't know, your -- your own son?
好
Okay.
让我为你们展示设备本身
Let me show you the device itself.
医生办公室只需
All a doctor's office has to do
把它插入接待处电脑的USB接口
is plug this into the USB slot of their reception room computer.
病人打开手机上的应用
A patient opens the app on their phone
接着用手机碰触设备
and taps it against the device.
然后你们看
And just like that,
所有你们加密和相关的
all of your encrypted and pertinent
医疗及保险信息
medical and insurance information
便即刻出现在医生的数据库里
is instantly in your doctor's database.
真抱歉 二位
Well, I am so sorry, guys,
但我就喜欢填医疗表格
but I like filling out medical forms,
我想还有数百万
and I think there are millions of
辛勤工作的美国人跟我一样
hardworking Americans just like me,
所以我这个投资大鲨[投资真人秀]退出
so this Shark is out.
老妈
Uh, Mom?
祝你好运攻下她
Oh, good luck with that one.
她可比我难对付多了
She's a lot tougher than me.
我接下来要说的话不会为我带来一丝快乐
Well, it brings me absolutely no joy to say this.
卢克 你太牛掰了
Luke, I'm impressed.
-可是呢 -没有可是
- But...? - But nothing.
你知道
Do you have any idea
我有多讨厌填那些破医疗表格吗
how much I hate filling out those medical forms?
看起来你真的做了很多功课
It seems like you have really done your homework,
而且最重要的是 你有个很棒的搭档
and most importantly, you got a great partner here.
大胆去做吧
I say go for it.
你认真的吗
Seriously?
克莱尔
Psst, Claire?
尼克从斐济打来找你
Um, I have Nick on the phone from Fiji.
我们在忙没空接 玛格丽特
We're in the middle of something, Margaret.
他说有急事
He says it's an emergency.
他打的是我的手机
He's on my phone.
在日光浴室里
It's in the solarium.
那是飘窗而已 玛格丽特
It's a bay window, Margaret.
我们做到了 兄弟
We did it, buddy!
等一下 先别急着抱
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on.
这事还没定下来呢
It's not settled yet.
刚才不是听到有人首肯了吗
Well, I thought we heard a yes.
不 我还要跟我太太商量一下
No, I'm -- I'm still having a conversation with my wife.
你先放轻松坐好
Please, make yourself comfortable.
要不把你那双胶底鞋脱了
Maybe kick off those rubber-soled shoes
我去给你拿杯即时速冻冷饮
while I grab you an instantly cold beverage.
"我是你老公啊" "你老公啊"
"I'm just your husband." "Oh, your husband?"
"你在八卦 我最喜欢八卦了"
"You're gossiping. That's what I do."
某人似乎刚吵完架哦
Looks like someone had a fight.
你好 帕斯特纳克太太
Hey, um, Mrs. Pasternack.
有这么明显吗
Um, was it that obvious?
我见到谁都这么说
Eh. I say that to everyone.
多半时候都说对了
More often than not, I'm right.
喝马天尼吗
Martini?
不用了谢谢 我很好
No thanks, I'm -- I'm good.
不 你才不好
No, you're not.
婚姻好难
Marriage is hard.
我知道啊
I know!
每个人都总想要改变对方
Everyone's always trying to change each other.
就好像 我是成人电影导演
It's like, I'm an adult film director
喜欢收集宝贝时光牌的可爱娃娃
who collects Precious Moments Dolls.
让我随心做自己吧
Let me be me!
你们俩闹什么矛盾了
So, what's up with you two?
小卡开始找其他州的工作
Uh, Cam started looking for a job out of state
却没有事先跟我商量
with-- without consulting me.
别担心 你会遇见其他良人的
Don't worry. You'll meet someone else.
不 他希望我跟他一起去
No, he wants me to go with him.
这才是我认识的小卡
Ah, that's the Cam I know.
他天天念叨的都是你
He's always going on about you.
是吗
He is?
你从没看过他的脸书主页吗
Haven't you ever seen his Facebook page?
他迷死你了
He's obsessed with you.
"这张照片里的米奇尔多好看"
"How gorgeous does Mitchell look in this picture?"
"能和一个为正义而战的人结婚真骄傲"
"Proud to be married to a man who fights for justice."
"米奇尔的感冒好了
"Mitchell over his cold.
希望我老公今晚能跟我好好腻乎一下"
Hope my hubby brings the love tonight."
我爸给这条点赞了 恶心
Ew, my dad liked that. Euch.
好吧 莉莉 我要去看比赛了
All right, Lily, I'm on my way to the game.
情况很糟吗
How bad is it?
大爸快被海豚虐死了
The dolphin is eviscerating Dad.
如果是我被虐 他肯定会想办法
Oh, if it was me, he would totally do something.
可我该怎么做 给我个提示[标牌]
But what?! Ah, just give me a sign!
老天爷 有没有花点钱就能解决的办法
Is there any way I could just throw money at it?
除了拉米雷斯神父
Except for Father Ramirez,
我问的每位牧师
all the priests I asked
都觉得秘密受洗"不太妥当"
were "Uncomfortable" with my secret baptism.
说这事"基本和绑架一样"
They said it was "borderline kidnapping,"
还说我的小诡计"像魔鬼一样"
that they found my trickery "devilish."
天主教什么时候这么爱评判人了
It's like, when did Catholics become so judgmental?
杰 你回来了
Jay, you're back!
你为什么听起来这么诧异
Why do you sound surprised?
像没指望我能活着回来似的
You cut my brakes or something?
家里为什么有个牧师
What the hell's a priest doing here?
不过是来检查一下
Oh, it's just a check-up.
宝宝之一或许被附身了
One of the babies maybe is...possessed.
等等 你要瞒着海莉和那个谁
Wait, are you baptizing them behind Haley
让宝宝们受洗
and what's-his-name's back?
你不能对别人的孩子这样做
You can't do that to other people's kids!
没什么大不了的
It's not a big deal.
有用的话 宝宝们会受到保护
If it works, the babies are protected,
她们的灵魂就安全了
their souls are safe,
可以在天堂直到永远
and they're gonna spend eternity in Heaven.
如果没用
If it doesn't,
就像洗了个澡一样
it's just like I gave them a little bath.
"老"字我听得懂
"Viejo." I know that word.
这位时间老人居然说我老
Did Father Time here just call me old?
好了 我们冷静点
Okay, let's all calm down.
让宝宝们投入唯一的真神的怀抱
Let's introduce the babies to the one true God,
然后一起吃些咖啡蛋糕
then we'll have some coffee cake.
你知道你这么做过分了
You know you're crossing a line here.
不用让海莉和迪兰知道
Haley and Dylan doesn't even have to know.
知道什么
Know what?
家里为什么有个牧师
Why is there a priest here?
我跟你说过 茵素被附身了
I told you, Poppy's possessed!
除了你别人都看出来了
Everybody can see it but you.
你就问问我们不行吗
Why didn't you just ask us?
我问过 我问过你
I did. I did ask you.
你答应了 我想你当时喝得很醉
You said yes. I think you were very drunk.
海莉 新菲尔
Haley, New-Phil,
你们真的想让孩子受洗吗
do you really want this baptism?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们没怎么想过这个问题
We've barely thought about it.
迪兰确实说过会研究一下宗教的事
Dylan did say that he was going to research some religions.
吉姆·琼斯纪录片我刚看了一半
I'm halfway through this Jim Jones documentary.
目前觉得那个宗教挺酷的[是个邪教]
So far, that religion seems pretty cool.
很抱歉我没事先问你
I'm sorry that I didn't ask you before.
我真的想让乔治和茵素受洗
I really wanted to do this for George and Poppy.
受洗会让他们的灵魂
Baptism is gonna allow their souls
找到永恒的平和
to find eternal peace.
有什么代价
What's the catch?
总是要捐款
Well, there's a lot of donations
还要为性爱感到羞耻
and some shame around sex,
但圣诞节很热闹
but Christmas is fun.
我都不知道该怎么决定
I don't even know how I can decide,
但我想没什么大问题
but I guess it can't hurt.
你们能去天国了
You're going to the kingdom of Heaven.
在那 你们会与人类最优秀的灵魂相遇
And there, you're going to join the souls of some of our greats,
例如圣女贞德 特蕾莎修女
like Joan of Arc, Mother Theresa,
丹尼·德维托也早晚会死
Danny DeVito when he dies.
开始吧
Go.
好的
Yes.
-等等 等等 等等 -又怎么了
- Wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. - What now?
不好意思
Well, I'm sorry.
只是 这突然间变得好真实
It just -- It suddenly just got very real,
让他做完就是感觉不对
and it does not feel right to end,
我不知道为什么
and I don't know why,
外公 是我反应过度了吗
Grandpa, am I making too much of this? I --
别问他 因为他根本不信上帝
Don't ask him because he doesn't even believe in God.
我只是不觉得
I just don't think
人需要教堂和袍子那些东西
you need church, costumes, all that stuff
来感受神圣的力量
to feel a higher power.
但你相信它的存在
But you think there is one?
是的 我在孩子们出生时感受到了
Yeah, I felt it when my kids were born,
当我遇到这个想共度一生的疯女人
and, um, when I met this crazy woman here
我也感受到了
that I want to spend the rest of my life with,
但也可以是日常小事
but, you know, it can be just a normal everyday thing, too.
好比我听到棒球飞进手套时
You know, like the way it makes me feel
所体验的那种感觉
when I hear a baseball thump into a mitt
或是汤姆·威兹的声音
or the way Tom Waits' voice
莫名地难听又好听
can somehow be ugly and beautiful at the same time.
你明白我的意思吗
Am I making any sense?
去年 迪兰和我去了优胜美地国家公园
You know, last year, Dylan and I went to Yosemite,
某个清晨我们很早就醒了
and we woke up really early one morning,
我们静静望着那些峻美的群山
and it was just us and those gorgeous mountains,
那么多参天大树 大鹿带着小鹿
a bunch of huge trees, and a family of deer.
是那么美好
It was so beautiful,
让我觉得我和某种更伟大的能量
and it made me feel like I was connected
联系在了一起
to something bigger than myself.
或许某天
You know what, maybe one day
我们会让他们在教堂受洗
we can get them baptized in a church,
但现在
but for now,
我们何不带他们去优胜美地国家公园
why don't we take them up to Yosemite
然后仰望天空说谢谢
and look up and say thank you?
听上去是个很棒的计划 海莉
That sounds like a great plan, Haley.
是啊
Yeah.
你在那里的时候可以烤些棉花糖
And maybe roast some marshmallows while you're there
这样他们就会习惯接近火[地狱]了
so that they get used to being around fire.
不 尼克 你不能一直从市场部拿钱
No, Nick, you can't keep taking money from marketing.
他们需要
They need --
什么
What?
你在度假的时候
No, I will not stay on the phone
我不会和你一直保持联系
while you moon a cruise ship.
你是
Are you --
-克莱尔 -等等
- Claire? - Hang on.
克莱尔
Claire.
那是什么
What was that out there?
我以为我们是一队的
I thought we were supposed to be on the same team.
我们是啊
We are. I --
他们有个好主意
They've got a great idea.
你只是嫉妒因为卢克去了斯库特那里
You're just jealous because Luke went to Scooter
而不是来找你
and not to you.
才不是
That is not true.
真的吗 你不觉得他们有点东西吗
Really? You don't think they're on to something?
是个很棒的想法 好吧
It's an amazing idea. Okay.
但他为什么不来找我
But why didn't he come to me?
因为你爱我所做的一切
Because you love everything I do.
我想确定这真的是个好主意
I wanted to make sure this was actually a good idea.
这个想法太机智了
That is so smart.
怎么会有人这么帅又...
How is someone this handsome --
我想说的是
Okay, this is what I'm talking about.
我喜欢和你一起发明 但这是生意
I love inventing with you, but this is a business.
斯库特有很多经验
And Scooter has a lot of experience.
这并不代表
That doesn't take away from
我们共同创造的一切就不重要
all of the things that we've made together.
是它们带领我走到了现在
All of that stuff brought me here.
-真的吗 -表格填写器的拼写少不了Phil[菲尔]
- Really? - You can't spell FormFiller without Phil.
但你知道是可以的吧
But you know you can, right?
他很伤心 我是在安慰他
The man's hurting. I'm throwing him a bone.
真为你骄傲 卢克
I'm proud of you, Luke.
见鬼 我也为斯库特骄傲
Damn it, I'm proud of Scooter, too.
哇
Wow.
看到你们报告想法时
You know, seeing your guys' pitch,
眼中闪耀的狂热还有热情
and the -- the passion, that sparkle in your eye,
我都不记得上次见你
I -- I don't remember the last time
这么在乎一件事是什么时候了
I saw you care about anything that much.
我也不记得我上次是什么时候
I don't remember the last time I did.
这真是太伤人了
That's super hurtful.
没有 亲爱的 我指的是工作
No, sweetie, I'm talking about work.
说实话 我以前早上起床的时候
I -- Honestly, I used to get up in the morning,
我迫不及待地要上班
and I couldn't wait to get to the office.
现在我感到害怕
And now I dread it.
没错
I do.
我怀念热爱工作或者喜欢工作的日子
I miss loving my job or even liking it.
现在我做的就是为别人擦屁股 处理投诉
Now all I do is put out fires and manage complaints
还因为一些无关紧要的
and -- and lose sleep over stuff
事情而失眠
that really doesn't matter.
是啊 我想我
Yeah. I think I'm --
我想我要辞职了
I think I'm gonna quit my job.
你说真的吗
Are you serious?
是的
Yeah.
这疯狂吗
Is that -- Is that crazy?
没有 倒不是
Uh, no. No, not necessarily.
我的意思是 疯狂是坚持
I mean, crazy is sticking with something
做一件让你痛苦几个月的事情
that's been making you miserable for months
而现在有很多公司
when there are so many companies out there
都想要你这样的人才
who would want someone with your skills.
尼克 你还在吗
Hey, Nick, you still there?
我今天早上告诉我儿子 他不应该放弃
I told my son this morning that he should never quit.
我错了
Well, I was wrong.
我退出
I'm out.
天哪 感觉太好了
Aah! That felt so good!
太可怕了 但感觉太好了
It was so scary, but it was so good.
我也真为你骄傲
I'm so proud of you, too!
听着
Hear, hear!
致我们下一场冒险
To our next adventure!
我在酒窖里找到的
Oh, I found this in the wine cellar.
那是个地下室 玛格丽特
It's a basement, Margaret.
快 快 超过他
No, no, close the gap!
球 球 球 球 球
Ball, ball, ball, ball, ball!
简直是场噩梦
It was a nightmare.
这是我职业生涯中最大的机会
The biggest opportunity of my career,
而我无法集中
and I couldn't focus.
我尽量不做出任何可笑的动作
I tried not to make any mockable movements.
大卫·达西的水平太高了
David Tashi was just operating at too high a level.
但后来奇妙的事情发生了
But then something wonderful happened.
天哪 你打我
Oh. You hurt me.
就在那时 我意识到我认识那只鸡
That's when I realized I knew that chicken --
那弱弱的拳头
those weak punches,
体育课时脸上写着"最后再来选我"的小跑
a run that said "pick me last" in gym class.
那是我的米奇尔
It was my Mitchell.
大伙 过来 围过来 集合
Okay, guys, come on! Let's huddle up. Huddle up.
我们离开那里 好好打比赛
Let's get out there and play our hearts out.
走吧 走吧 快过来
Let's go, let's go! Bring it in!
皮特科夫斯基 快来
Pitkowski, come on.
那边更有意思吗
Something more interesting going on over there?
是啊 还有人能看见
Yeah, does anybody else
海豚和鸡在打架吗
see the dolphin fighting the chicken?
因为我之前头被狠狠的打中过
'Cause I got hit pretty hard in the head earlier.
好了 过来
All right, let's go.
我们接下要这么做
All right, so this is what we're gonna do.
我们上场 我们要断
We're gonna go up, right, you're gonna be cutting...
爸爸在哪里
Where's Daddy?
他去还小鸡服了
He went to go return the chicken costume.
那是两个小时前的事情了
That was like two hours ago.
你不会认为
You don't think...
米奇尔
Okay, Mitchell?
吉祥物里是你吗
Is that you in the mascot costume?
有人逼你这么做吗
Is someone forcing you to do that?
那就赶紧上车
Okay, then get in the car now.
我住在加利福尼亚
I stayed in California.
我的婚姻违背了我的宗教信仰
I married outside of my religion.
我醒着的时候都和你家人在一起
I spend every waking moment with your family.
但我的爱不是无条件的
But my love is not unconditional.
好的
Oh, Okay.
我喜欢人们朝我按喇叭
I love it when they honk from me.